<resources>
    <string name="app_name">WITchar17</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_robotics">Robotics</string>
    <string name="title_activity_project">Project</string>
    <string name="title_activity_paper">Paper</string>
    <string name="title_activity_cool_code">CoolCode</string>
    <string name="title_activity_event_data">EventData</string>
    <string name="hotel"><b>For Boys:-</b>\n\nT-4,BLossomeResidency,\nAshok Chowk Solapur\nMaharashta-413006\n\n<b>Faculty Coordinator</b>\nM.R F.R Sayyed\n\n<b>Student Coordinator</b>\nAkash Dabrase</string>
    <string name="girls"><b>For Girls:-</b>\n\nT-4,W.I.T Girls Hostel,\nNear Ashok Chowk Solapur\nMaharashta-413006\n\n<b>Faculty Coordinator</b>\nM.R D.S Patil\n\n<b>Student Coordinator\nSukanya Hazare</b></string>
    <string name="develo">The WITchar-2K17 would like to acknowledge the team of developers.</string>
        <string name="aboutUs1"><b>About WIT:-</b> S.A.P.D.J. Pathshala Trust, established in the year 1885, has now completed its 130 years of service in education. Originally started with the objective of imparting religious education to students, the trust gradually moved into the field of general education and established High Schools. Trust successfully runs 13 institutions, employing around 722 staff with around 12000 on-campus students.

\n\nS.A.P.D.J. Pathshala Trust started Walchand Institute of Technology (W.I.T.) in July 1983, which is appropriately named after Seth Walchand Hirachand, one of our country\'s pioneer of industrial development. W.I.T. runs 6 undergraduate courses, 4 post graduate courses and Doctoral programme in Electronics, Civil, Computer Science, Electronics and TeleCommunication and Mechanical Enginnering with excellent results. The institute has a strong network of 160 dedicated faculty members, with around 22000 motivated students. MNCs recruit students from the institute on a large scale. The institute is accredited by N.B.A. New Delhi and awarded \'A\' grade institute by State Government of Maharashtra and is acclaimed worldwide.</string>

    <string name="aboutUs2"><b>About WITChar:-</b> A National Level Technical Symposium organised by WIT, Solapur. It is being held every year since 2007. Since its inception, it has gained immense response. It provides a platform to all the budding engineers to showcase their talent. Student from every nook and corner of the nation participate with great enthusiasm every year. This year too, we invite people from all over to become a part of this technical voyage and have a great experience. See you at WITchar - 17. "
</string>

    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="skip">Skip</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="Accomodation1">- Free accommodation will be provided to outstation participants on <b>17th 18th 19th March</b>\n\n- Participants are required to bring their own <b>blankets</b>\n\n- Participants should reach the campus on <b>their own</b>\n\n- Outstation participants should request for accommodation through<b> website or android app</b>\n\n<b>- Check out the registration link below.</b></string>
    <!--************************************** All Events Names Here- Total 21***********************************************-->
    <string-array name="allinOne">
        <item>ASquare</item>
        <item>ApTech Quiz</item>
        <item>Catia Champ</item>
        <item>Cool Coding</item>
        <item>Dream CAD</item>

        <item>Electron Mechanics</item>
        <item>Energy Contraption</item>
        <item>Graphity</item>
        <item>InfraCivil</item>

        <item>Expert MANu </item>
        <item>Network Treasure Hunt </item>
        <item>Paper Presentation</item>
        <item>Project Competition</item>

        <item>Poster Making</item>
        <item>Quizotronics</item>
        <item>Robotics</item>
        <item>STADD War</item>

        <item>Web Imagica</item>
        <item>Wonder Tender</item>

        <item>Google It</item>
        <item>Logo Quiz</item>

    </string-array>


    <!-- //********************************Basic Info of  all Events Here**************************************************************/  -->
    <string-array name="Basic_Info">

           <item>
             <!-- 1.ASquare-->
               Do you possess skills in JAVA, XML and ECLIPSE? Are you confident in your Android
            know-how? Do mainstream Android tasks make you scoff in derision?\n\nWell, worry not, for we bring you
            a two stage war to ascertain whether your boasts hold merit or are you just another second rate keyboard beater. Android Picassos ahoy!
           </item>


        <item>
             <!-- 2.ApTech Quiz-->
            Face against levels of progressively more mind-bending aptitude and civil tech questions in a two tiered quiz
		show complete with pretty anchors and loud buzzers to reach the final stage and maybe win some fame and
		glory to your name along the way. Let the builders do the telling!
            </item>


          <item>
              <!--3.catia champ-->

              Plan, model, draft and assemble wondrous mechanical miscellanea on a deadline using CATIA V3 fuelled by the
		mechanical beast within.\n\nCreate the design of all designs to trump definitively over the rival
		rookies and pave the way to systematic domination over their battered and broken tools.
		 Terms and conditions apply.

          </item>

        <item>
          <!--4. cool coding-->
        </item>

        <item>
         <!-- 5..Dream CAD  -->
            If you’re the sort to heap righteous critique to those ill-designed nonsensical design plans that fail to reach the
            meager expectations one would unwittingly dare have of them, then YOU sir/ma’am are the one we’ve been waiting for to make
            a designing wonder that’d drive reviewing critics into frenzy. Or are you?
        </item>

        <item>
         <!-- 6. Electron Mechanics  -->
            If you say you are a student of the Electronic age, then we’d say that you show us some justification.
            How? This two stage event will test your circuit making capabilities and be a proof of why electronics is a
            stream youthful and eternal. Just don’t blow up any ICs in the process, in your head or otherwise.

        </item>

        <item>
         <!-- 7. Energy Contraption  -->
            Usually the task of drawing a circle is an act that requires all the
			complex skill and physical dexterity of a 5 year old.\n\nNow, add a limit to the number of possible direct
			interactions, maximum energy efficiency and a limited six by six area and we have an interesting
			situation in our hands. Oh and do not forget about the time limit! Believe yourself to be creative?
			Be the best at this very simple task to know for real.

        </item>

        <item>
         <!-- 8. Graphity  -->
            Are you an artist in the bones of an engineer? Do picturesque results please you infinitely more
            than grey mundane data outputs? Then we invite you to show us if your strokes are really genius or are
            you just another Bob Ross proclaiming dirt stains as heavenly immortal works of art. This two round
            elimination cum computer graphics generation contest will certainly verify.
        </item>

        <item>
         <!-- 9. Infra Civil -->
            Any rear scratching cave-dwelling cretin can make a craggy cave to keep the sun and the rain at bay.
            It requires the hands of a master to give birth to a structure so majestic, it stops being a building and
            starts being a monument. And that is the truest path to immortality for the apprentice in the trade of the brick
            and mortar. Are you Eiffel enough?
        </item>


        <item>
            <!-- 10. Menu Expert -->
            Be tested on the disciplines of the mech! If you can answer the riddle of mechanical steel - and whatever else
		the rules decree, you must then plan for the heroic quest by writing arcane mech sequences and formulae.
		The ultimate challenge for the worthy ones shall be the test of the birth of THE COMPONENT!


        </item>

        <item>
         <!--11. Network Treasure Hunt-->
            Want to be a pirate and ride the whimsy ocean waves in quest for treasure but the open sea and lack of - ironically
            – flowing water make you shudder and go green in the face?\n\n
            Fear not matey!  For we have a treasure hunt that’d be
            just as exhilarating – only without the added dirt, sweat, nasty grog or risk of undue dismemberment. And it’s on
            a computer while sitting in an air-cooled room too!
        </item>


        <item>
       <!--12 Paper Presentation-->

        </item>



        <item>
       <!--13 Project Presentation-->

        </item>


        <item>
         <!--14.Poster Making-->
            Sounds simple yes? Just like the showing poster template of some favorite ad or movie or some such right?
            I’d urge you to guess, again.\n\n
            This competition involves not flights of bumbling fantasy but rather a
            representation of your technical perception on the issues provided. And in a physical form no less.
            So go ahead, make a technical poster. If you can that is.

            </item>

        <item>
         <!-- 15. Quizotronics -->
            "Yes you need to preferably belong to either the electronics or telecommunications department to enter this thing.It is indeed a woefully uninspired naming choice that can be attributed to murky tradition. It’s a tech quiz competition. Need we say more?
        </item>


        <item>
         <!--16.Robotics -->


        </item>


        <item>
         <!--17. STADD War  -->
            It’s not so much a war of armies as it is the designing of stable trusses for the armies to fight
            upon and the ground to not collapse under their collective load and ruin the awesome fight sequences.\n\nSo go ahead,
            make an awe-inspiring battlefield capable of hosting glorious confrontations.

        </item>


        <item>
         <!-- 18. Web Imagica -->
            What, I ask you, frequent your lives in greater quantities – pages, or web pages? Websites are numerous in
            quantity and consequently, web pages more so. The same cannot however be said of the quality criterion.\n\nSo come.
            Come and make a web page so ‘worthy’, that it’d  be worthy of Thor’s hammer – or alternatively, one that’d make the
            internet proud.
        </item>





        <item>
         <!-- 20.Wonder Tender -->
            So as the rules say, you have to do the best tender. This is assumedly for the civil society and as such,
            the competition complexities can be inquired at the very professional coordinators, assuming you are in the game
            to win that is?

        </item>


         <item>
            <!--Google It-->
             We know and we have seen the tests that - no matter the complexity - crumble in the face of deceit and cunning. But what if the skill of deceit is the
		 one being tested? What if cunning is not a shorter path, but rather, the ONLY path?\n\nWe humans cheat, steal and lie our way through our
		 entire existances - by innocence or guilt, for inspiration or desperation, in life and death. So we present to you a challenge where the known
		 world\'s\ greatest treasure is stored. We DARE you, to Google it!
        </item>


        <item>
            <!--Logo Quiz-->

        </item>


    </string-array>
    <!--***************************************Rules Section**********************************************************-->
    <string-array name="Rule">


 <item>
         <!--1.ASquare -->
     <b>Round-I:\t\t           Duration - 30 minutes</b>\n
1. In this round, total 30 Multiple Choice Questions test will be conducted and time duration will be 30 minutes.\n
2. These MCQs will be formed based on the basic concepts of Android and Java Programming.\n
3. This test will be attended by group of two participants.\n
4. Qualifying teams will be eligible for Round-II.\n\n


<b>Round-II:\t\t         Duration - 3 hours</b>\n


1. In this round, specific app design and its implementation task will be given to a group.\n
2. Participants will be completing given app development within 3 hours using Android Programming language.\n
3. Participants can use Android docs for program implementation.\n
4. Any external source used for the event will lead to disqualification of the group.\n
5. Marks will be given based on different parameters like UI representation, UI elements used, Look and Feel, GUI design, Logic, presentation, comments, etc.\n\n

<b><i>Participants will be provided with the necessary software tools as mentioned below:</i></b>\n
1. Android SDK components and a version of the Eclipse IDE
     with built-in ADT (Android Developer Tools) to streamline your Android app development.\n\n
2. The ADT Bundle includes everything you need to begin developing apps:-\n
o Eclipse + ADT plugin\n
o Android SDK Tools\n
o Android Platform-tools\n
o The latest Android platform\n
o The latest Android system image for the emulator.\n\n

     1. Maximum participants: 2 per team.\n
     2. Registration fees:200/- per team.



        </item>


        <item>
             <!-- 2.ApTech Quiz-->

            1.	Two rounds - Elimination round and Final round.\n
2.	Both the rounds consist of Aptitude and Technical questions.\n
3.	Calculator is allowed only in Final round.\n
            4. Maximum participants : 2 per team\n
5. Registration fees : Rs. 200/- per team\n

            </item>


        <item><!--3.catia champ-->

            1. This event is an Individual event and the task completion with the use of CATIA V5 R19.\n
            2. Task completion will be in TWO stages.\n\n

<b>Stage 1:</b> Part modeling and Drafting.   (Time 1 Hour)\n
The participants who will complete 1st stage those will be qualified for the Stage 2.\n\n

<b>Stage 2:</b> Assembly (Time 1 Hour)\n\n

3. Competition time : 1 Hour / stage\n\n

4. Evaluation:\n
\t\ti)	Completion of the provided task.\n
\t\tii)	Completion time.    \n\n

 5. Registration Fees: 200/- per participant.


        </item>



        <item>
         <!-- 4.Cool Code-->
            </item>

        <item>
         <!-- 5.Dream CAD-->
            1. Students have to plan a marriage hall and prepare AutoCAD drawing for it.\n\n
            2. Maximum participants: 2 per team.\n\n
            3. Registration fees: Rs. 200/- per team.\n\n

        </item>

        <item>
         <!--6.Electron Mechanics -->
            1. Electron mechanics is a Circuit Building Competition.\n
2. Contest conducted in two rounds : \n
3.	Qualifying round: MCQ type, Shortlisted candidates will move on to final round.\n
4.	Final round : Circuit Building \n
5.	Topic for design will be given on the spot.\n
6.	Maximum participants: Two members per team.\n
7.	Name of the participants entered in the registration forms shall be considered final.\n
8.	Registration Fees: Rs. 200/- per team.\n




        </item>

        <item>
         <!--7.Energy Contraption -->


            <b> Final Task:</b>\n\n
            Draw a circle of radius min 5 to max 10 cm.( Paper will be provided .)
\n\n
<b>Contraption Rules:</b>\n\n
1.	The minimum and maximum time for contraption is 2 minutes and 10 minutes respectively. After 10 minutes,
            30 points per minute will be deducted from the total score.\n
2.	The team will be disqualified if they exceed permissible number of hand touches in the contraption.\n
3.	Final decision made by judges and organizers will be binding to all.\n
4.	No alteration in any step will be allowed during the trial of the contraption.\n
5.	A space of 6ft.*6ft.*6ft. (l*b*h) will be provided to each team.\n\n


<b>General Rules:-</b>\n\n
1. Maximum 4 participants per team.\n
            2. Only 230V AC power supply and Task set up will be provided by organizers.\n
3. Reporting time for the team is 7.30AM and actual event (judging) will start
            at 10.00AM. Before that each team should prepare their complete setup.\n
4. Team can perform intermediate task to gain bonus points. These are not compulsory tasks.\n
5. Only 4 hand touches are allowed (with deduction of 30 points each), team with more than 4
            hand touches will be disqualified.\n
5. Only one chance is allowed to complete the process.\n
6. Use of explosives is not allowed. \n
7. Team should submit their soft copy of abstract on or before 18th March.\n
            8. Registration Fees: Rs 400/- per team.\ n
9. Area provided will be 6 feet x 6 feet x 6 feet.\n
10. The format of abstract is available on website \n\n


11. It’s mandatory to follow the same set up as per the submitted abstract. \n
12. Participants are requested to bring 3 copies of properly printed abstract and submit one copy at the time of event. \n
13. Decision given by the judges will be final. \n
14. All rights are reserved with organizers. \n\n





Marking scheme:- \n\n

NOTE: - \n
Main task i.e. drawing Circle on paper should be on the last conversion of your contraption, it must not occur any where in the middle of contraption\n








Total points= [A x 20] + [B x 10] + [C] + [D x100] – [E x30] + [F]\n
Where, \n
A= Number of distinct energy conversions \n
B= Number of conservations \n
C= Completion of main task \n
D= Extra ordinary conversion ( given below).\n
E= Number of hand touches. (Max 4). \n
F = Bonus points (includes completion of intermediate task). \n
Team completing task within 2 minutes will gain bonus 30 points.\n \n

INTERMEDIATE TASKS \n
Intermediate tasks are not compulsory. To gain bonus points team can perform intermediate task.\n
Difficulty level \n
Easy *\n
Medium **\n
Difficult ***\n
No of tasks that can be performed\n
1-3\n
1-2\n
1-3\n
1.\n
Burst balloon\n
Dominoes display\n
Move an object in a vertical loop.\n
2.\n
Play music\n
Blow a balloon\n
Open a filled carbonated beverage bottle using opener.\n
3.\n
Spray deodorant \n
#Create sound using a row of pendulum.\n
#Display a single digit number on paper.\n
4.\n
Blow a candle\n
Make an object fly in air.\n
#Open and close the cap of bottle.\n\n




Cutting of Fruit\n\n


Note:-  \n
#1- Minimum 4 pendulums must be used in a row and the sound must be clearly audible to judge.\n
#2- You have to display a number using pen, ink or color and the digit displayed must be in English and must not be “1”.\n
#3- The bottle used for opening and closing the cap must be normal packaged drinking water bottle.\n
Parallel steps for intermediate tasks are allowed.\n
Scoring Scheme: -   Each easy task carries 30 points.\n
		          Each medium task carries 60 points.\n
		          Each difficult task carries 100 points.\n

        </item>

        <item>
         <!-- 8. Graphity -->
            Rules:\n

1. A Task will be given to a group.\n
2. Participants can use any one of the language(c, c++, java) to complete given task.\n
3. The specified task must be completed within 3 hours.\n\n


General Instruction:\n

1. Maximum 2 participants per team.\n
            2. Registration fees: Rs. 200/- per team\n
3. Any external source used for the event will lead to disqualification of the group.\n
4. Marks will be given based on different parameters like logic, presentation, comments, etc.\n
5. Students must bring their valid college identity card while coming for the event.\n
6. Any team that is not present at the specified time will be disqualified.\n
7. Rules may be change without prior information.\n


           </item>


        <item>
         <!--9.InfraCivil-->
            1. Maximum participants : 2 per team\n

2. Prepare a model of a othropedic hospital at the venue using mount board and adhesives.\n
3. Prepare the municipal plan for the same.\n
4. The assessment of model will be based on use of planning, principles, bye-laws and
            skill of model making with equal weight age. (33% each)\n
             6. Registration fees : Rs. 200/- per team\n

        </item>

        <item><!--10.Manu Expert-->

            <b>Round-I: \t\tDuration:30 min</b>\n\n
            1. Objective type questions will be there.\n
2. Questions will be related to machine tool processes, process engineering, machine drawing, tool engineering,
            metrology and quality control etc. \n\n

<b>Round-II:\t\tDuration:30 min</b>\n\n
            1. Component drawing will be given.\n
2. Students have to write operations sequence, machine required, measuring instrument required.\n\n

<b>Round-III:\t\tDuration:60 min</b> \n\n
            1. Students have to carry out machining operations on to produce component as per drawing.\n
            2. Dimensional accuracy and surface finish has prime important.\n\n


            <b>General Rules:</b>\n\n
            1. Maximum participation: 2 from SE(MECH), TE(MECH), BE(MECH)\n
2. Registration fees Rs. 400/- per team\n
3. Judges decision will be final.\n
4. Organizers have full right to change the rules as per the situation and requirement.\n


        </item>

        <item>
         <!--11. Network Treasure Hunt-->
            1. The game asks you to solve the puzzles or questions and find out the treasure on computers.\n
2. Questions may be based on general aptitude, puzzle or games like miniclip. \n
3. The participants who succeed to solve all puzzles will be selected for next round based on the set criteria.\n
4. The elimination will be strictly based on total time taken and the number of puzzles solved by participants.\n
            5. Participant should participate Individually\n
            6. Registration fees is 200/-

Based on the no. of participants Elimination round shall be conducted in stages, following which all elimination round winners would be eligible for Final round.\n

        </item>

        <item>
              <!--12. Paper Presentation-->

        </item>

        <item>
         <!--13.Project  Competition-->

            1.	Maximum 2 participants are allowed (Food coupons will be given to only two candidates but certificates will be issued for 4 candidates per team).\n
2.	Participants are required to display the project for 2 days.\n
3.	Bring A3 size poster of your project for displaying.\n
4.	Candidate should submit 1 copy of project synopsis at the time of reporting.\n
5.	Respective College identity card is mandatory.\n

        </item>

         <item>
         <!--14.Poster Competition-->
             Topics for  ( Technical poster making competition ) Witchar 2017\n\n

1.	Role of technology in developing smart city.\n
2.	E- waste recycling.\n
3.	Effect of demonitization on technology growth.\n
4.	Removing carbon footprints on the earth (providing energy sources that produces less carbon CO2 and also saving energy)\n
5.	Internet of things (IOT) for social benefit.\n
6.	Role of NFC (near field communication)  in recent technology development.\n\n

             <b>Description of Your Event:</b>\n\n
This competition involves no highly decorative creativity but rather your creativity of representing your technical perception regarding the issues provided. Show your skills and talent neatly on the sheet.\n
And go ahead with your idea.\n
<b>Rules for Event:</b>\n\n
1.Maximum participants 2 per team.\n
2.the poster may include text, diagrams, pictures, photos from magazines, newspaper related to their topics. However cutting ,pasting etc. should be done at the time of competition.\n
3.Participants should confirm their entry number from the student co-ordinator which will be used as the identity of poster. No other identity of participants should be on the poster.\n
4.Participants will get 2 and ½ hours to complete their poster.\n
5.Topics of poster will be display one week before the competition.\n
6.Entry fees is Rs 200 per team.\n
7.Participants must come with their drawing material and ideas. Drawing sheet of A1 will provided.\n\n



         </item>


<item>
         <!--15.Quizotronics-->


    Maximum participants:2 per team. \n\n

    <b>Round-I: Goggle It\t\t\tDuration:10min</b>\n\n

    1. students are allowed to search the answers on internet.\n
2. No negative marking.\n
3. Shortlisted students will proceed to Round-II. \n\n


    <b>Round-II: Techno-Quiz\t\t\tDuration:20min</b>\n\n


The technchnical questions are based on fundamental knowledge of Electronics and Telecommunication Engg.\n\n

	    <b>Round-III: Finale Battle</b>\n\n
	It consists of 4 rounds\n

	<b>Round 1:</b>Pass – on Round\n
In this round each team is asked 2 questions. \n
For each correct answer team gets 10 marks else question is passed to next team. \n
For each successive pass two marks less are awarded to each team.\n



<b>Round 2:</b> Picture Perception Round\n
Two pictures are shown to each team and questions based on that are asked.\n
For each correct answer team gets 20 marks.\n
1
<b>Round 3:</b> Buzzer Round\n
Total 10 questions are asked in this round. \n
After completion of each question the team can press buzzer to answer the question. \n
For correct answer the team gets 20 marks and for wrong answer -10 marks.\n

    <b>Round 4:</b> Rapid Fire Round\n\n
Each team will be asked 10 questions in 1 minute. \n
After completion of 10 questions if time is remaining the unanswered questions will be repeated.\n
For each correct answer the team gets 5 marks.\n\n

From final round out of 5 teams top 3 highest scored teams will be awarded prizes.

Registration fees Rs. 200/- per team

</item>

        <item>
         <!--16. Robotics-->
        </item>

        <item>
         <!--17.STADD War-->

            1. Students have to prepare structural framing plan for design pin jointed roof truss.\n
2. Analyze and Design a roof truss using suitable structural analysis and design software.\n
3. Structure will be assessed based on Codal provisions, economy and safety and serviceability.\n
4. Maximum participants: 2 per team.\n
5. Registration fee: Rs. 200/- per team.\n

        </item>

         <item>
         <!-- 18. Web Imagica -->

             <b>Description of Your Event:</b>\n\n
1. A Group of Maximum Two Participants.\n
2. Event will be of Two Rounds.\n
3. First Round will be ELIMINATION ROUND.\n
4. In Second Round a 4+ page website is to be designed within 3 hours, based on the topic which will be announced on the day of the competition.\n
5. Participants can use HTML5, CSS, JQuery, PHP, JSP, ASP.net or any other language for web development.\n
6. Participants will be provided with the necessary software tools such as: Dreamweaver, Notepad++, Photoshop, and MySQL.\n

<b>Round-I:</b>\n\n
1. It will be a HOMEPAGE designing round. All the participants should design a start page of the website in 30 min of time
             provided.\n
2. Qualifying teams will go for Round 2.\n\n
<b>Round-II</b>\n\n
1. Design a 4+ page website based on the topic which will be announced on the day of the competition.\n
2. Participants can use HTML5, CSS, JQuery, PHP, JSP, ASP.net or any other language for web development\n\n

             <b>Software tools:</b>\n\n
1. Web Development:\n
a) Dreamweaver\n
b) Notepad++\n
c)Visual Studio\n\n

2. Image/Graphic:\n
a) Photoshop/images\n\n
3 Database Connectivity:  MySQL ,MS ACCESS\n\n

1. Website should not contain any material deemed to be objectionable.\n
2. Maximum Participants:2 per team.\n
3. Students must bring their valid college identity cards while coming to the event.\n
4. Any team that is not present at the specified time will be disqualified.\n
5. Rules may change without prior intimation.\n
6. Participants who need other than above tools , should inform the coordinators two days before the contest\n\n
             Registration fees Rs. 200/- per team.

         </item>


        <item>
         <!-- 20. Wonder Tender-->
            1.  Maximum participants: 2 per team.\n
2. Registration fees: Rs. 200/- per team.\n
3. Tender notice will be published on our website 8 days before the competition.\n
4. Tenders shall be opened on the date of competition in presence of referees.\n
5. The best tender will be awarded.\n

        </item>

        <item>
            <!--Google it-->
            1. Participants are expected to maintain decorum. We reserve the right to disqualify any participant found misbehaving.

2. In case of disputes the decision of event heads and judges will be final and binding to all.

3. Structure and rules of event may be changed without prior intimation, Participants are requested to check the website regularly for updates.

4. Participants are requested to bring ID proof like college I-Card and a smartphone with them. No external equipment other than mentioned above and provided by organizers can be used.

5. The venue of the event will be informed to the participants accordingly.

6. The participation is individual and no teams can be formed.

7. A participant can take part more than once.

8. The prizes for this event will be given on the spot.

Event Structure:

15 questions to be answered in 20 minutes using Google.

How to play:

The participant will have to search for the answers to the given questions on Google and
            write the answer accordingly. Internet access will be provided by the organisers.
            The answers can only be searched on the smartphone and the participant cannot use
            any other electronic device like laptop etc


        </item>


        <item>
1. Participants are expected to maintain decorum. We reserve the right to disqualify any participant found misbehaving.

2. In case of disputes the decision of event heads and judges will be final and binding to all.

3. Structure and rules of event may be changed without prior intimation, Participants are requested to check the website regularly for updates.

4. Participants are requested to bring ID proof like college I-Card and a smartphone with them. No external equipment other than mentioned above and provided by organizers can be used.

5. The venue of the event will be informed to the participants accordingly.

6. The participation is individual and no teams can be formed.

7. A participant can take part more than once.

8. The prizes for this event will be given on the spot.

Event Structure:

30 logos to be recognized in 15 minutes.

How to play:

The participant will be given a sheet of paper and logos will be projected on a screen.
            The participant has to identify the logo and write their company name or the brand name whichever is
            applicable on that sheet of paper. The logos will be from various fields like IT companies, food companies, fashion,
            airlines, android apps and many more. You may download logo quiz apps from play store for your preparation.

        </item>


    </string-array>


    <!--************************************** All Respective Event Faculty Names Here***********************************************-->
    <string-array name="Faculty_Name">
        <item> <!--Asquare-->Prof. Mr P.N. Kathawate</item>
        <item><!--ApTech Quiz-->Prof. T. Meenakshi </item>
        <item><!--Catia Champ-->Prof.P.G. Chitte</item>
        <item><!--Cool Coding--></item>
        <item><!--Dreama CAD-->Prof. S.B. Thalange </item>

        <item><!--Electron Mechanics-->Ms. A.V. Thalange </item>
        <item><!--Energy Contration-->Prof. Mrs. R.J. Shelke </item>
        <item><!-- Graphity-->Prof. Mrs. S.K. Karpe</item>
        <item><!--Infra Civil--> Prof. S.K. Kulkarni</item>

        <item><!--Manu Expert-->Prof. D.J. Doshi</item>
        <item><!-- Network Treasure Hunt -->Mr. Patnaik P.D.R. </item>
        <item><!--PPt--></item>
        <item><!--Project P.--></item>

        <item><!-- Poster -->Prof. Mrs. R.A. Attar</item>
        <item><!--Qiuiz  -->Mrs. V.S. Kulkarni</item>
        <item><!--  Robotics-->Mr.R.D. Mistry </item>
        <item><!-- STADD WAR-->Prof. C.G. Konapure</item>

        <item><!-- Imagica -->Prof. Mrs. S.S. Ambarkar</item>
        <item><!--Wonder Tender  -->Prof. S.B. Gosavi</item>


        <item><!--Google It  --></item>
        <item><!--Logo Quiz --> </item>
    </string-array>


    <!--************************************** All Respective Event Student Names Here***********************************************-->
    <string-array name="Student_Name">
        <item> <!--Asquare Ms.--> Manohar Kudkyal</item>
        <item><!--ApTech Quiz-->Basavraj P</item>
        <item><!--Catia Champ-->Sourabh Patil</item>
        <item><!--Cool Coding--></item>
        <item><!--Dreama CAD-->Shubham Wadapurkar </item>

        <item><!--Electron Mechanics-->Ms. Dipali J. Madanwale</item>
        <item><!--Energy Contration-->Ms.Dipti Jayaprakash Kore</item>
        <item><!-- Graphity-->Kirti Jadhav</item>
        <item><!--Infra Civil- -->Lakhan Baxi</item>

        <item><!--Manu Expert-->Mr. Aditya Waikar</item>
        <item><!-- Network Treasure Hunt-->Ms. Apurva Patwardhan</item>
        <item><!--PPt--></item>
        <item><!--Project P.--></item>

        <item><!-- Poster-->Deepika Jain</item>
        <item><!--Qiuiz-->Ms. Godhe Riya</item>
        <item><!--  Robotics-->Swapnil Patil</item>
        <item><!-- STADD WAR-->Bhakti Nawale</item>

        <item><!-- Imagica-->Rashmi Rao</item>
        <item><!--Wonder Tender-->Nilesh Pendpale</item>

        <item><!--Google It--></item>
        <item><!--Logo Quiz--></item>

    </string-array>

    <!--******************************************All Respective event's Faculty Mobile No.****************************************************-->

    <string-array name="Faculty_Mobile">
        <item> <!--AsquareProf. Mr P.N.Kathawate-->9763709600</item>
        <item><!--ApTech Quiz-->9975035376</item>
        <item><!--Catia Champ-Prof.P.G.Chitte-->9028193550</item>
        <item><!--Cool Coding--></item>
        <item><!--Dreama CAD-Prof. Thalange S.B.-->9423065244</item>

        <item><!--Electron Mechanics-Ms. Thalange A.V.-->9922399811</item>
        <item><!--Energy Contration-Mrs. Shelke R.J.-->9423331596</item>
        <item><!-- Graphity-Prof. Mrs. S.K. Karpe-->8055514289</item>
        <item><!--Infra Civil-Prof. S. K. Kulkarni-->9561568456</item>

        <item><!--Manu Expert-Prof. D.J. Doshi-->9422025706 </item>
        <item><!-- Network Treasure Hunt-Mr. Patnaik P.D.R. -->9421068108</item>
        <item><!--PPt--></item>
        <item><!--Project P.--></item>

        <item><!-- Poster-Prof. Mrs. R.A.Attar -->8446508006</item>
        <item><!--Qiuiz-Mrs. Kulkarni V.S  -->8378981404</item>
        <item><!--  Robotics-Mr.R.D.Mistry-->9822217799</item>
        <item><!-- STADD WAR-Prof. C.G. Konapure-->9423065280</item>

        <item><!-- Imagica-Prof. Mrs. S.S Ambarkar-->9420546769</item>
        <item><!--Wonder Tender-Prof. S.B. Gosavi -->9822402069</item>


        <item><!--Google It  --></item>
        <item><!--Logo Quiz --></item>

    </string-array>


    <!--************************************** All Respective Event Student Mobile No. Here***********************************************-->

    <string-array name="Student_Mobile">
        <item> <!--Asquare Bhavana Penta -->7840953494</item>
        <item><!--ApTech Quiz-->9604231883</item>
        <item><!--Catia Champ-Mr. Saurabh Patil-->8625997955</item>
        <item><!--Cool Coding--></item>
        <item><!--Dreama CAD-Shubham Wadapurkar -->9890150754</item>

        <item><!--Electron Mechanics-Aishwarya Mehta-->9561841176</item>
        <item><!--Energy Contration-Prashant Kore-->7276702520</item>
        <item><!-- Graphity-Kirti Jadhav-->7058052677</item>
        <item><!--Infra Civil-Lakhan Baxi-->9001962727</item>

        <item><!--Manu Expert-->9405078348</item>
        <item><!-- Network Treasure Hunt-Akash Kamboj-->9405614129</item>
        <item><!--PPt--></item>
        <item><!--Project P.--></item>

        <item><!-- Poster-Deepika Jain -->9049592750</item>
        <item><!--Qiuiz-->8237377804</item>
        <item><!-- Robotics-Mr.Swapnil Patil -->9665266498</item>
        <item><!-- STADD WAR-Bhakti Nawale-->9156910569</item>

        <item><!-- Imagica-Rashmi Rao-->9637126759</item>
        <item><!--Wonder Tender-Nilesh Pendpale  -->9890863778</item>


        <item><!--Google It --></item>
        <item><!--Logo Quiz--></item>

    </string-array>


    <!--**********************************************Project **********************************************************-->

<string name="project_basic_civil_info">
    Feel that your exceptional talents of creation and presentation are wasted on the theoretical muck of the Civil higher-ups?
    Tired of wasting your though processes doing the same old same old till your IQ pulse seems to flatline? Think that you contain that shuddering
	spark that\'s just waiting to be fed the fuel of defiant obfuscation to escalate into the roaring inferno that\'ll sear your name into history old
	and unforgotten?\n\n
	Why not make a project instead then?

</string>

<string name="project_basic_cse_info">

       Feel that your exceptional talents of creation and presentation are wasted on the theoretical muck of the CSE higher-ups?
    Tired of wasting your though processes doing the same old same old till your IQ pulse seems to flatline? Think that you contain that shuddering
	spark thats just waiting to be fed the fuel of defiant obfuscation to escalate into the roaring inferno that\'ll sear your name into history old
	and unforgotten?\n\n
	Why not make a project instead then?
</string>

<string name="project_basic_mech_info">
 Feel that your exceptional talents of creation and presentation are wasted on the theoretical muck of the Mech higher-ups?
    Tired of wasting your though processes doing the same old same old till your IQ pulse seems to flatline? Think that you contain that shuddering
	spark thats just waiting to be fed the fuel of defiant obfuscation to escalate into the roaring inferno that\'ll sear your name into history old
	and unforgotten?\n\n
	Why not make a project instead then?
</string>


<string name="project_basic_eln_info">
  Feel that your exceptional talents of creation and presentation are wasted on the theoretical muck of the Electronics higher-ups?
    Tired of wasting your though processes doing the same old same old till your IQ pulse seems to flatline? Think that you contain that shuddering
	spark thats just waiting to be fed the fuel of defiant obfuscation to escalate into the roaring inferno that\'ll sear your name into history old
	and unforgotten?\n\n
	Why not make a project instead then?
</string>



<string name="project_basic_civil_rule">

        1.	Civil Engineering projects by students of SE/TE/BE.\n
2.	Not necessarily final year projects.\n
3.	Projects in any of the sub-branches of Civil Engineering.\n
4.	Software based projects are also allowed.\n
    5. Submit your project synopsis on the link given below or through website\n\n


</string>

<string name="project_basic_cse_rule">
        1.	Open for Engineering Students (Se to Be) of above mentioned groups\n
2.	Models/design/prototype/concept/simulation based on project is/are allowed\n
3.	Bring two hard copies of synopsis.\n
4.	Synopsis should contain the details of the group\n
5.	Project demonstration is must. If unable to demonstrate , go for paper presentation\n
6.	Requirements for project display should be clearly mentioned\n

7.	Registration fee: Rs.300/per project.\n
8. Maximum participants: 2 per team.\n
9.	 For all communication include group name as a  part of subject\n
10.  Each team will be provided a time limit of 20 minutes.\n
11.	Each participant should speak and explain about the project.\n
  12. Submit your project synopsis on the link given below or through website\n\n

    </string>

<string name="project_basic_mech_rule">
        1. Mechanical Engineering projects by students of SE/TE/BE.\n
2. Not necessarily final year projects.\n
3. Projects in any of the sub-branches of Mechanical Engineering\n

4. One set of hardcopy of the synopsis should be brought by the participants on the day of event.\n
5. Registration fees: Rs. 300/- per Project.\n
6. Maximum participants: 2 per team.\n
    7. Submit your project synopsis on the link given below or through website\n\n
    </string>


<string name="project_basic_eln_rule">

        1. Electronics and Allied branches engineering projects by students of SE/TE/BE.\n
2. Projects in any of the sub-branches of Electronics Engineering.\n
3. Software based projects are also allowed.\n
4. Registration fees: Rs.300/- per Project.\n
        4.Maximum participants: 2 per team.\n

5.Bring one hard copy of synopsis.\n

6. Synopsis should contain the details regarding group.\n
7. Project demonstration is must. (At least partial fulfilment of project objective)\n
8. Requirements for project display should be clearly mentioned.\n
 9. Submit your project synopsis on the link given below or through website\n\n
</string>
    <!--*******************************************************Multiple Events- Project************************************************************************-->
    <string-array name="project_base_info">
        <item>@string/project_basic_civil_info</item>
        <item>@string/project_basic_cse_info</item>
        <item>@string/project_basic_eln_info</item>
        <item>@string/project_basic_mech_info</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="project_rules">
        <item>@string/project_basic_civil_rule</item>
        <item>@string/project_basic_cse_rule</item>
        <item>@string/project_basic_eln_rule</item>
        <item>@string/project_basic_mech_rule</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="project_faculty">
        <item>Prof. M.G Kalyanshetty</item>
        <item>Mrs. Dixit. R. K.</item>
        <item>Mrs. Mergu R.R.</item>
        <item>Dr.S.R.Dulange</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="project_student">
        <item>Vishal Dadibude </item>
        <item>Ankita Mantri</item>
        <item>Mr. Ayush Jain  </item>
        <item>Mr. Vyankatesh Metgiri</item>

    </string-array>


    <string-array name="project_faculty_Mobile">
        <item>9422646598</item>
        <item>9850563472</item>
        <item>9422461564</item>
        <item>9421953485</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="project_student_Mobile">
        <item>8421520107</item>
        <item>9765828748</item>
        <item>8390942601</item>
        <item>8149605621</item>

    </string-array>
    <!--*******************************************************Multiple Events- Paper************************************************************************-->
    <string-array name="paper_base_info">
        <item>@string/Paper_civil_basic_info</item>
        <item>@string/Paper_cse_basic_info</item>
        <item>@string/Paper_eln_basic_info</item>
        <item>@string/Paper_mech_basic_info</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="paper_rules">
        <item>@string/Paper_civil_basic_rules</item>
        <item>@string/Paper_cse_basic_rules</item>
        <item>@string/Paper_eln_basic_rules</item>
        <item>@string/Paper_mech_basic_rules</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="paper_faculty">
        <item>Prof.  S. C.Deshmukh</item>
        <item>Mrs. Dixit. R. K.</item>
        <item>Mr. S.B Jamge</item>
        <item>Prof. Naik. S. B.</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="paper_student">
        <item>Pavas Jain</item>
        <item>Ankita Mantri</item>
        <item>Kirankumar Chincholi</item>
        <item>Mr. Raman Uplaikar</item>

    </string-array>


    <string-array name="paper_faculty_Mobile">
        <item>9923282288</item>
        <item>9850563472</item>
        <item>9822790360</item>
        <item>9850890208</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="paper_student_Mobile">
        <item>8087802926</item>
        <item>9765828748</item>
        <item>7709881219</item>
        <item>9960108484</item>

    </string-array>


    <!--*********************************************************************************************************-->

    <string name="Paper_civil_basic_info">
     Feel that your exceptional talents of research and discovery are wasted on the clerical agenda of the Civil higher-ups?
        Tired of wastingyour breath writing the same old same old till there is nothing left in your ink pot?\n\n
	 Think that you contain that shivering spark thats just waiting to be fed the fuel of
	 creative indulgence to escalate into the roaring inferno that\'ll sear your name into history long and unforgiven?\n
	Why not write a paper about it then?


         </string>

    <string name="Paper_cse_basic_info">
Feel that your exceptional talents of research and discovery are wasted on the clerical agenda of the CSE higher-ups?
        Tired of wastingyour breath writing the same old same old till there is nothing left in your ink pot?\n\n
	 Think that you contain that shivering spark thats just waiting to be fed the fuel of
	 creative indulgence to escalate into the roaring inferno that\'ll sear your name into history long and unforgiven?\n
	Why not write a paper about it then?
    </string>

    <string name="Paper_mech_basic_info">
 Feel that your exceptional talents of research and discovery are wasted on the clerical agenda of the Mech higher-ups?
        Tired of wastingyour breath writing the same old same old till there is nothing left in your ink pot?\n\n
	 Think that you contain that shivering spark thats just waiting to be fed the fuel of
	 creative indulgence to escalate into the roaring inferno that\'ll sear your name into history long and unforgiven?\n
	Why not write a paper about it then?
    </string>

    <string name="Paper_eln_basic_info">

 Feel that your exceptional talents of research and discovery are wasted on the clerical agenda of the Electronics higher-ups?
        Tired of wastingyour breath writing the same old same old till there is nothing left in your ink pot?\n\n
	 Think that you contain that shivering spark thats just waiting to be fed the fuel of
	 creative indulgence to escalate into the roaring inferno that\'ll sear your name into history long and unforgiven?\n
	Why not write a paper about it then?

    </string>


    <string name="Paper_civil_basic_rules">

           <b>Topics:</b>\n
     1.  Modern urban transport system\n
2.  Disaster management in flood/earthquake/tsunami and other natural disaster\n
3.  Ground improvement techniques for stable civil engg. structures\n
4.  Advanced materials of constructions\n
5.  Modern construction techniques in civil engg.\n
6.  Water resource management for suitable development.\n
7.  Computer aided analysis and design in structural engg / water resource Geo-technical engg. and environment engg.\n
8.  Geographical and informational system for civil engg problem solving\n
9.  Recent advances in structural/Geo-technical/water resource/ environmental/transportation/construction engg.\n\n



     <b>General Rules:</b>   \n
1.	Paper should be maximum 12 pages of A-4 size, typed in Times New Roman, font size 12, line spacing 1, strictly in
        IEEE format.\n
2.	Total presentation time for Team will be Max. 10 mins, 8 mins for presentations and 2 min for Question-Answer session.\n

3.	Bring two hard copies.\n

4.  Registration fees: Rs. 300/- per team.\n
5.  Maximum participants: 2 per team.\n
        6. Submit your paper abstract on the link given below or through website\n\n



    </string>

    <string name="Paper_cse_basic_rules">

       <b>Topics:</b>\n

1. Data Science and  Data Analytics\n
2. Internet of Things Applications –IoT\n
3. Security in Cloud Computing\n
4. Deep Learning in Neural Network\n
5. Augmented Reality and Virtual Reality\n
6. Soft Computing Techniques\n
7. Computational Neuroscience\n
        8. Wireless Networking\n
        9. Intelligent Chat Bots\n\n

        <b>General Rules:</b>\n
1. Paper should be maximum of 6 pages of A-4 size, typed in Times New Roman, font size of    12,line spacing 1,IEEE format.\n

2. Bring a hard copy with you.\n
3. Maximum participants : 2 per team.\n
4. Registration fees : Rs. 300/-per team.\n
5. Each team will be provided a time limit of 15 minutes.\n
         6. Submit your paper abstract on the link given below or through website\n\n


    </string>

    <string name="Paper_mech_basic_rules">

        <b>TOPICS:-</b>\n

1. Cryogenics.\n
2. Nanotechnology.\n
3. Production Prototyping.\n
4. Mechanical Engineering Design\n
  \tA. CAD/CAM/CAE/FEM\n
  \tB. Ergonomics\n
5. Robotics\n

  \tA. Automation\n
   \tB. Mechatronics\n
   \tC. MEMS\n\n


<b>General Rules:</b>\n
1. Paper should be maximum 12 pages of A-4 sizes, typed in ‘Times New Roman’, font size 12, line spacing 1,
        strictly IEEE format.\n
2. Total presentation time for team for will be maximum 10 mins,8 mins for presentation and 2 mins. for Question-Answer session.\n

3. Bring 2 hard copies.\n
4. Registration fee: Rs. 300/- per paper.\n
5. Maximum participants: 2 per team.\n
 6. Submit your paper abstract on the link given below or through website\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="Paper_eln_basic_rules">

         <b>Topics:-</b>\n

        1. Image and Video Processing\n
2. VLSI/ULSI Design and Fabrication\n
3. Radio and Satellite Communication\n
4. E-waste Management\n
5. Embedded System Design\n
6. Optical Communication\n
7. System on Chip (SoC)\n
8. Ad-hoc Network\n
9. Speech Processing\n
        10. Internet Of Things\n
        11. Augmented Realities\n
        12. Power Electronics\n\n

<b>General Rules:</b>\n

1.	Paper should be maximum 6 pages of A-4 size, typed in Times New Roman, font size 12, line spacing 1,
        strictly in IEEE format. \n

2.	Bring two hard copies. \n

3.	Registration Fee: Rs. 300/- per paper.\n
4.  Maximum Participants: 2 per team.\n
         5. Submit your paper abstract on the link given below or through website\n\n
    </string>

    <!--*******************************************************Multiple Events- Coding************************************************************************-->
    <string-array name="code_base_info">
        <item>@string/Marathone_Basic_Info</item>
        <item>@string/Matlab_Basic_Info</item>
        <item>@string/Microcontroller_Basic_Info</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="code_rules">
        <item>@string/Marathone_Rules</item>
        <item>@string/Matlab_rules</item>
        <item>@string/Microcontroller_rules</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="coolcodename">
        <item>Code Marathon</item>
        <item>Matlab Contest</item>
        <item>Micro-Controller</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="code_faculty">
        <item>Prof. Mrs. K.V.Kumavat</item>
        <item>Mr. A. S. Gundale</item>
        <item>Mr. V. H. Kondekar</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="code_student">
        <item>Sonali Shendge</item>
        <item>Ms. Aishwarya Anand Nanna  </item>
        <item>Ms. Smita Bargale</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="code_faculty_Mobile">
        <item>9637619995</item>
        <item>9422461564</item>
        <item>9860148150</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="code_student_Mobile">
        <item>9370411223</item>
        <item>8862069707</item>
        <item>9405962739</item>
    </string-array>
    <!--*******************************************Single Single Strings Sections**************************************-->
    <!--code-->
    <string name="Marathone_Basic_Info">
    To know the code, to hasten the coder, to hasten the code. Only mastering one of the holy disciplines of
		the virtual language shall one be ready to face this challenge.
		The skill to breathe life into the mundane has long been the trade of the engineer. With the coming of the
		info age, this has moved into virtual environments for genesis.\n\n So, will you be the one to be truest
		codemeister of them all?
    </string>


    <string name="Matlab_Basic_Info">

To have the wisdom of the path of the circuit and to have the skill to the creation of the ciruit, that
		is the way of the ECAD warrior!
		The skill to breathe life into the mundane has long been the trade of the engineer. with the coming of the
		info age, this has moved into virtual environments for genesis.\n\n So, will you be the one to be truest
		circuit breaker of them all?
    </string>


    <string name="Microcontroller_Basic_Info">

           The art of taking life might be flashy indeed, but it is the creationists that make what would
			never die; C for yourself if the KEIL (c51) favors you and whether the shape-shifting god of
			prophesies - PROTEUS - shall be your guide.
			The skill to breathe life into the mundane has long been the trade of the engineer with the coming of the
			info age, this has moved into virtual environments for genesis.\n\nso, will you be the one to be truest
			puppeteer of them all?

    </string>


    <string name="Marathone_Rules">

Programming Contest ( 19th March 2017)\n\n


            <b>Round-I: Aptitude\t\t     	Time: -	9:00 AM to 10 AM</b>\n
1. An online MCQ test.\n
2. The test would comprise of questions from Programming Techniques using “C” and Logical Reasoning.\n
3. Negative marking system.\n\n

<b>Round-II: Fast Coding\t\t		Time: -	11:00 AM to 12 PM
</b>\n

1.  You will be given 6 programs, out of which you have to implement 3 programs as early as possible to qualify for Final round.\n
2.  ACM ICPC format.\n\n
<b>Final Round: Smart coding\t\t             Time:-	12:30 PM to 1:30 PM
</b>\n
1.	You will be given 1 problem statement to implement.\n
2.	Time and Space complexity will be strictly considered.\n\n

<b>General Rules:-</b>\n
        1. The programs can be written in any programming language (C, C++, Java).\n

 2. The participants will have to face a Panel of Judges in the final round and should be able to justify their logic and code.\n
 3. Decision of the Judges will be final.\n
 4. The organizers reserve the right to make changes to the event program.\n
 5. Participants must carry a valid college ID card during the event.\n
 6. Candidate have to ensure their presence strictly as per the timing of the event.\n
 7. Registration fees: Rs. 200/- per team\n
 8. The team of maximum 2 members.\n
    </string>


    <string name="Matlab_rules">


<b>Round I-Qualifying Round</b>\n
1.	Multiple choice questions - duration of 30 minutes and no negative marking\n

2.	Questions are based on basic MATLAB \n\n



<b>Round II -Final Programming Round</b>\n
1. Programming task to be completed on provided PC. \n
 2. Final task is to be performed using basic MATLAB only, use of toolbox is prohibited.\n
3. Teams are allowed to use MATLAB help. \n\n

Evaluation  is based on completion of task, optimization of MATLAB code and visual output \n

Note- Participants should bring their college Id-Card at the time of contest\n\n



<b>General Rules:</b>\n
1. Contest open for all students (FE to BE) of all branches of engineering. \n
2. Maximum two participants per team. \n
        3. Registration fees: Rs. 200/- per team\n
4. Contest is of two rounds- Qualifying Round and Final MATLAB Programming Round \n
5. Qualified teams from round one will be participating the final programming round \n
\n\n

<b>Note-</b> Participants should bring their college Id-Card at the time of contest

    </string>



    <string name="Microcontroller_rules">


       •	A Team may consist of maximum of 2 members\n
        •Registration fees: Rs. 200/- per team\n
•	Use of calculators is allowed. \n
•	Mobile phones and any electronic/mechanical gadgets is strictly prohibited during elimination round.\n
•	Hardware kit or simulator required for design will be provided by organizers. \n
•	Decision of judges will be final and binding to all.\n

    </string>

    <!--*******************************************************Multiple Events- Robotics************************************************************************-->
    <string-array name="robotics_base_info">
        <item>@string/line_seguidor_basic_Info</item>
        <item>@string/ifyoucan_basic_Info</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="robotics_rules">
        <item>@string/line_seguidor_rule</item>
        <item>@string/ifyoucan_rules</item>

    </string-array>


    <string-array name="robonames">

        <item>Deadly Follower</item>
        <item>2 Fast 2 Furious</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="robotics_faculty">
        <item>Mr. R. D. Mistry</item>
        <item>Mr. R. D. Mistry</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="robotics_student">
        <item>Mr. Dipesh Shah </item>
        <item>Mr. Dipesh Shah </item>

    </string-array>


    <string-array name="robotics_faculty_Mobile">
        <item>9822217799</item>
        <item>9822217799</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="robotics_student_Mobile">
        <item>7588103140</item>
        <item>7588103140</item>

    </string-array>

    <!--**********************************************Robotics***********************************************************-->
    <string name="line_seguidor_basic_Info">
       " The mechanical electricians take on popular children game 'follow the leader'; Creating a bot to follow about the black line of fate to whichever
 		way the whimsical examiners prompt.\n\n
        Think that making puny splotches of clumsiness on a computer is for the weak?
        Are you too hardcore for the virtual world?\n\nThen this gentleman/lady is your chance to construct a
        construct so constructive that its construction spews forth destruction upon the crude toasters that those
        other wannabe robotics ‘savants’ fumble to assemble. It’s the ROBOT WARS!"

    </string>

   <string name="ifyoucan_basic_Info">
Its an obstacle course. For robots! Also, bring your own batteries.\n\n
        Think that making puny splotches of clumsiness on a computer is for the weak?
        Are you too hardcore for the virtual world? Then this gentleman/lady is your chance to construct a
        construct so constructive that its construction spews forth destruction upon the crude toasters that those
        other wannabe robotics ‘savants’ fumble to assemble. It\’s the ROBOT WARS!

    </string>

    
        <string name="line_seguidor_rule">

        <b>Problem Statements:-</b>\n\n
Autonomous bot should follow the given track.\n\n

<b>Robot Specifications:-</b>\n\n
1. The robot should be completely autonomous with required mechanical set up to complete the task.\n
2. Remote controlled or wired robot is not allowed.\n
3. The dimensions of the robot should not exceed 20cm*20cm.\n
4. Ready-made gearboxes, sensors, development board can be used.\n\n

<b>Power Supply:</b>\n\n
1. The voltage between two points should not exceed 12V.\n
2. Battery should be mounted on the bot and should be brought by the participants themselves.\n
3. Charging facility will be made available, though it is advised to bring along charged Batteries.\n\n
     <b>Robo track wil be updated on 12 March </b>\n


<b>Rules:</b>\n\n

1. The objective of the game is to complete the track in the least possible time and earn maximum points while completing the given task.\n
2. The next round would include a selected number of teams on the basis of their rankings decided in the previous round.\n
3. In case of any tie, a common task would be given on the spot to both the teams and winner would be decided on the basis of best timing and points in that task.\n
4. In case there is tie (even after the task completion) then the match will be restarted.\n
5. There will be multiple rounds.\n
6. If the teams Autonomous robot does not make to the destination in the given time, then the winner will be decided on the basis of points\n
7. The matches for the knock out rounds will be decided by a proper scheme told by the referees at that time and will be binding.\n
8. No programming of BOT will be allowed in middle of match, the bot must start again from the last covered check-point.\n
9. No Lego kits are allowed.\n


    </string>

    <string name="ifyoucan_rules">
        <b>Problem Statement</b>\n\n
Design remote controlled ROBOT that must cover maximum distance in shortest possible time overcoming various obstacles.\n\n

<b>Robot Specifications</b>\n\n
1.The L X B should not exceed 30 X 30 cm.\n
2.The net weight should not exceed 10 kgs.\n
3. Power source may or may not be on board.\n
4.Wired or wireless robot are allowed\n
5.The maximum allowed voltage to power the robot is 24V.\n\n


<b>Rules</b>\n\n

1. The team should not consist of more than 3 members.\n
2.Each member from same college is not mandatory\n
3.No test practice will be allowed on the main arena.\n
4.Terminals for charging the battery will not be provided in the college\n
5. Registration fees : Rs. 300/- per team.\n
    </string>


    <string-array name="Out_of_box_basic_info">
        <item>
 <!--Google It-->
            We know and we have seen the tests that - no matter the complexity - crumble in the face of deceit and cunning. But what if the skill of deceit is the
		 one being tested? What if cunning is not a shorter path, but rather, the ONLY path?\n\nWe humans cheat, steal and lie our way through our
		 entire existances - by innocence or guilt, for inspiration or desperation, in life and death. So we present to you a challenge where the known
		 world\'s\ greatest treasure is stored. We DARE you, to Google it!
        </item>

        <item>
             We know that you have all played that one game where you have to guess the famous name by the famous logo.
            It is after all with millions of downloads in its name on the stores. And we know that you know that you have searched
            and guessed and teamed-up your way through the entire guess list.\n\n
		Well lets not let all that genuine effort and dedication be in vain!
		So we - the \'out-of-the-box\' people - present to you - the pro logo detective - a chance to have fun and make some glorious cash out of your \'skills\'!
        </item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="outboxstud">
        <item>Raj Chakraborty</item>
        <item>Saksham Jain</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="outboxcont">
        <item>7066147646</item>
        <item>7066147716</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Out_of_box_basic_rules">
        <item>
 <!--Google It-->

            <!--Google it-->

            <b>Event Structure:</b>\n\n

15 questions to be answered in 20 minutes using Google.\n\n

<b>How to play:</b>\n\n

The participant will have to search for the answers to the given questions on Google and
            write the answer accordingly. Internet access will be provided by the organisers.
            The answers can only be searched on the smartphone and the participant cannot use
            any other electronic device like laptop etc\n\n

            <b>General Rules:</b>\n\n
             1. Participants are expected to maintain decorum. We reserve the right to disqualify any participant found misbehaving.\n

2. In case of disputes the decision of event heads and judges will be final and binding to all.\n

3. Structure and rules of event may be changed without prior intimation, Participants are requested to check the website
            regularly for updates.\n

4. Participants are requested to bring ID proof like college I-Card and a smartphone with them. No external equipment
            other than mentioned above and provided by organizers can be used.\n

5. The venue of the event will be informed to the participants accordingly.\n

6. The participation is individual and no teams can be formed.\n

7. A participant can take part more than once.\n

8. The prizes for this event will be given on the spot.\n\n





        </item>

        <item>


<b>Event Structure:</b>\n\n

30 logos to be recognized in 15 minutes.\n\n

<b>How to play:</b>\n\n

The participant will be given a sheet of paper and logos will be projected on a screen. The participant has to identify
            the logo and write their company name or the brand name whichever is applicable on that sheet of paper. The logos
            will be from various fields like IT companies, food companies, fashion, airlines, android apps and many more. You
            may download logo quiz apps from play store for your preparation.\n\n


            <b>General Rules:</b>\n\n
            1. Participants are expected to maintain decorum. We reserve the right to disqualify any participant found misbehaving.\n

2. In case of disputes the decision of event heads and judges will be final and binding to all.\n

3. Structure and rules of event may be changed without prior intimation, Participants are
            requested to check the website regularly for updates.\n

4. Participants are requested to bring ID proof like college I-Card and a smartphone with them. No external equipment
            other than mentioned above and provided by organizers can be used.\n

5. The venue of the event will be informed to the participants accordingly.\n

6. The participation is individual and no teams can be formed.\n

7. A participant can take part more than once.\n

8. The prizes for this event will be given on the spot.\n




        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="Privacy"><b>Walchand Institute of Technology, Solapur (WIT)
Mobile Apps Privacy Statement</b>


Last updated: February 2017


WIT is committed to protect your privacy. This privacy statement governs your use of the WIT\'s Mobile Apps. It does not apply to other online or offline WIT\'s  sites, services, or apps.

<b>Collection and Use of Your Information:</b>

The WIT\'s Mobile Apps do not collect or transmit to WIT personally identifiable information or require the use of logins, passwords, etc. You are, however, offered the opportunity to participate in the App Rating Program. The App Rating collects information about your experience with application through rating of the application. We use this information to improve the quality, reliability, and performance of apps, and services.

<b>Security of Your Information:</b>

WIT respects and protects the privacy of the individuals who use WIT\'s Mobile apps and is committed to helping protect the security of your information. The application is, however, not capturing any individually identifiable information about you.

<b>Changes to this Privacy Statement:</b>

We will occasionally update this privacy statement to reflect changes in our products, services and customer feedback. When we post changes, we will revise the "last updated" date at the top of this statement. If there are material changes to this statement or in case WIT will use your personal information, we will notify you by a notification of such changes prior to implementing the change. We encourage you to periodically review this statement to be informed of how WIT is protecting your information. WIT welcomes your comments regarding this privacy statement. If you have questions about this statement or believe that we have not adhered to it, please contact us by email to principal.witsolapur@gmail.com or use the contact information provided below:


Walchand Institute of Technology, Solapur
P.B.No.634, Walchand Hirachand Marg,

    </string>


    <array name="reglink_paper">
        <item>
            https://script.google.com/macros/s/AKfycbzPzfhIuirhlGAPj2XjcuaeOfWBqb69GjZCTnqi3SUgp-I7aH4/exec
        </item>
        <item>
            https://script.google.com/macros/s/AKfycbzNIYeFQhCu3X8SYDq9M3rc62K1HM3pl26SaIgBQN9eKTWSfZzE/exec
        </item>
        <item>
            https://script.google.com/macros/s/AKfycbwwezqJcZdr3z_Fqmo7J8-TgnDoFUrjXDuMSwJ68Q4sLtPcsrlC/exec
        </item>
        <item>
            https://script.google.com/macros/s/AKfycbw8Hm1Wl2uWLeMdgPWOUwKMfJbBHYm_DbUMhM058mVW_cyV0EE/exec
        </item>

    </array>


    <array name="reglink_project">
        <item>
            https://script.google.com/macros/s/AKfycbzWGLpje1pJyQ-Yk3jJPpeuwvxWCH_QhZG-pF_SunvGfFWy1AY/exec
        </item>
        <item>
            https://script.google.com/macros/s/AKfycby0Az1STYpXwln2bSVZZuExnQAVSabmfLarTPbm353MBT285bI/exec
        </item>
        <item>
            https://script.google.com/macros/s/AKfycbyNkvjbBK2Qt5uvY8umJIhfGtMQ94_F6sizP1IwsqPehpAao4o/exec
        </item>
        <item>
            https://script.google.com/macros/s/AKfycbxrHpcclDDeNpqVsK2Y938uawTo3iGhBtDBt16KuAd0swHGDys/exec
        </item>

    </array>
    <string name="online">
        <b>About:</b>
\n\n A quiz that too very general in nature will be conducted on the android app of WITchar-16. Play it, the more you play, the more you get closer to the winning prize.\n sneak into the app for more details.\n\n
<b>Rules:</b>
\n\n 1.Everyday starting from 15th March,two new question will be posted on the android app,the user has to give the answers in the stipulated time.\n\n 2. For claiming the prize in this competition, in case you are the winner, you have to produce the receipt of any other event of which you have been a part, failing which you would not be eligible for the prize.\n\n 3.The prizes for this event will be given during the valedictory function\n\n
        <b>For any queries contact:-</b>\n\nPrajyot Gulhane\nMob no-9158228089\n</string>
</resources>






